https://www.jackite.com/policy

Jackite Return Policy
All products from Jackite are warranted for 90 days except damage caused by abuse, misuse or neglect.
Jackite requires the product be returned to Jackite for review before any consideration for refund, exchange or return can be determined.
Jackite does not recommend using the Jackite birds or poles in winds over 20 mph. Jackite’s Dove of Peace did fly through hurricane Bonnie.
For stores carrying Jackite products we offer an exchange program allowing you, the store, to test Jackite products in your market. You may exchange product that does not sell, dollar for dollar, for other products you wish to order. The returned product cannot be damaged or altered in any way including sales stickers or any other form of change. Jackite’s goal is to be able to return the product to inventory without any additional handling. All decisions are at the sole discretion of Jackite. Jackite may impose handling fees at its discretion.
For parts replacement for kites and poles:
1) For kites and poles purchased from Jackite, if parts required for assembly or normal use are missing, Jackite will replace parts free including shipping.
2) If kite and pole parts were lost due to purchaser’s error, please visit the parts page for details.
3) For Jackite Poles that have been damaged, Jackite requires the broken piece be returned. Jackite will, at its discretion, replace the parts for a small fee plus shipping.
4) For all other inquires for damaged products, Jackite requires the damaged product to be returned and possibly can replace the product or give a discount off future purchases.
Jackite  Privacy Policy
Jackite Inc knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information.
By visiting Jackite Inc, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does Jackite Inc Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Jackite Inc. Here are the types of information we gather
You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store features, and communication with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website.
E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "Subscription" preferences by logging into your account.
Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
Does Jackite Inc Share the Information It Receives?
Jackite respects your privacy and appreciates your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
Jackite works to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our products or services. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer by clicking the "log off" link located in the side menu.
Which Information Can I Access?
Jackite Inc gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit Jackite Inc, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Virginia. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past
Information You Give Us
You provide information when you search, buy, order, post reviews, or other methods of communication via our website or email to Jackite Inc. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and credit card information.
Automatic Information
For security purposes Jackite Inc sometimes collects and analyzes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for your protection for tracking purposes in the unfortunate event that someone gains access to your personal or financial information and opens an account, or makes purchases under your name.
Questions
Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu.
HomeAbout Jackite, Inc.DuPont TyvekUsing JackiteScarecrowWindsock FlyingAntennaCool DesignsHuntingOnline StoreBird Kites/WindsocksWindsock PolesMountsAccessoriesPartsInstructions/VideoArticlesVideosReviewsContactWholesaleShippingPolicy
Visit our
other company
www.LuckyDuckLanding.com
